https://houghi.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
What I think is usefull to put online. Most isn't.
Home
About
Contact
Privacy Policy
Search our site...
houghi.orgPrivacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: http://houghi.org.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
However no visitor is allowed to comment, so all the information above is useless.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
However no visitor is allowed to upload images, so the information above is useless.
Contact forms
Do not contact us. Not in any way. There are no contact forms.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
However visitor is allowed to login, or edit or publish anything. So the information above is useless.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Yeah, not doing that.
Who we share your data with
Not even myself, so basically nobody.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
But there is nothing to see.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
As nobody gets an account can leave comments, go elsewhere.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
There are no visitor comments.
Your contact information
We dont have a.
Additional information
How we protect your data
We do not have your data.
What data breach procedures we have in place
Panic and cry. I will be the website that is gone. We do not have your data.
What third parties we receive data from
Nobody
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
We do not have any data from you.
Local LinksHow to ask question on Reddit
Configuration
Connect over SSH
After the install
Backup
Bash script default start
Bash debugging
Banky on marketing
Starter distro
Installed Linux. Now what?
Categories
Linux
Random
Reddit
Search this site
Search our site...
Home
About
Contact
Privacy Policy
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
